Contact

R-10/151, Rajnagar, Ghaziabad 7011582252 (Work) sharmarohitt08@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rohit-sharma-18750b261 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
HTML5
Next.js
Computer Science

Rohit Sharma

Product Designer

Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

Summary

For the past three years, I have gained valuable experience in various fields, including UI/UX design, branding, graphics design, 2D motion graphics, animation, Blender-based 3D product promotions, and web development using HTML5, CSS, and JS.

In 2021, I had the pleasure of working for an EdTech startup that was then ranked among the top 10% of EdTech startups in India at that time.

Experience

Shree Vidyut Enterprises
Associate
January 2023 - December 2023 (1 year)
Delhi, India

Led a Demo Verticle: Crafted a distinctive UI/UX design for the website, contributed to development, and integrated AR functionalities for the featured product.

Optimized 3D Model Assets: Improved texture, redesigned, and optimized lighting for a provided 3D model, ensuring optimal display on the website.

Future Garages
UX Design & Web Development
June 2022 - July 2022 (2 months)
Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

During my time on a certain project, I had the responsibility of crafting a distinctive UI and UX design for the website, while also contributing to its development and integrating AR capabilities for the featured product.

Additionally, I was tasked with enhancing the quality of a 3D model provided by the project team by improving its texture, redesigning it, and optimizing its lighting for optimal display on the website. Precisely - The Opportunity Hub
UX Design & Animation
February 2021 - May 2022 (1 year 4 months)
Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

As part of my role, I created the UI/UX design for a product promotional campaign, as well as developing a working animation for the prototype.

Education

ITS Mohan Nagar Ghaziabad $\sqrt{}$ Bachelor's In Computer Applications - BCA , Computer Science · (March 2019 - July 2022)

Arena Animation

10+2, Animation, Interactive Technology, Video Graphics and Special Effects, 3D Modeling · (January 2017 - May 2021)